{
    "subject": "resource/The_Killing_Fields_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/screenplay",
    "object": "resource/Bruce_Robinson",
    "human_readable": "The screenplay of The Killing Fields (film) was written by Bruce Robinson.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9364925622940063,
            "question": "Who wrote the screenplay for The Killing Fields?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9203692674636841,
            "question": "What is the name of the film that Bruce Robinson wrote the screenplay for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9020816683769226,
            "question": "Is Bruce Robinson known for writing screenplays?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6344100832939148,
            "question": "Has Bruce Robinson written any other screenplays based on historical events?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6150925159454346,
            "question": "Can you name other films written by Bruce Robinson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47746536135673523,
            "question": "What awards or recognition did the screenplay for The Killing Fields receive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3100985884666443,
            "question": "How well-received was The Killing Fields by critics and audiences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27938538789749146,
            "question": "What genre is The Killing Fields likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23765824735164642,
            "question": "What historical events might have inspired The Killing Fields?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23078423738479614,
            "question": "What is the overall theme or message of The Killing Fields?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The screenplay of The Killing Fields (film) was written by Bruce Robinson.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7006_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What historical events might have inspired The Killing Fields?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7006_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is The Killing Fields likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7006_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How well-received was The Killing Fields by critics and audiences?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7006_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7006_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7006_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7006_138.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7006_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7006_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7006_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7006_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7006_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7006_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7006_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The answer is:\n\n```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis is because the documents contain information that confirms Bruce Robinson wrote the screenplay for the film \"The Killing Fields\", specifically in files path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7006/re-ranker-msmarco/126.txt` and `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7006/re-ranker-msmarco/135.txt`."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis answer is based on the information provided, which explicitly states that \"Bruce Robinson... was commissioned by David Puttnam to write the screenplay for Roland Joff\u00e9's The Killing Fields (1984)\" and \"Screenplay: Bruce Robinson\" in another document."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}